如果我们要继续住在这里
If we're going to be staying in this apartment,
你有没有兴趣把这里重新装修一下呢
would you be interested in doing a little redecorating?
其实呢  我还真愿意
Oh, actually, I would.
太好了  你有什么想法吗
Great, what'd you have in mind?
把对面公寓的每一件东西都搬过来
Let's take every single thing from the other apartment
然后放在这里面
and put it in here.
我们从小处开始着手如何
Well, how about we start a little smaller?
比如换下家具位置
Like moving the furniture around.
其实我一直认为
You know, I have always thought
这张沙发如果放在
that this couch would look fantastic
公寓口垃圾堆  一定棒呆了
on the curb in front of the building.
我们不能就这样把佩妮的东西扔掉
Look, we can't just throw away Penny's stuff,
但我们可以问她想不想把什么东西拿过去
but we can ask if she wants any of it back.
我想知道她会不会想要回这些挂画
You know, I wonder how she feels about all this artwork.
我确定她会很想念这张画
Well, I'm sure she misses this one.
这可是我此生送给别人最棒的礼物了
I mean, it's the greatest gift I've ever given anybody.
这画的确捕捉到了你与佩妮友情的美好
It truly does capture the beauty of your friendship with Penny.
而且这画可能还涨价了呢
It may have appreciated in value.
画完这画之后  那个画家就自杀了呢
The artist killed himself shortly after painting that.
这画不让她拿回去太说不过去了
Yeah, it seems only right that she have it back.
我都等不及看到她
I can't wait to see the look on her face
再度收到这画时的表情了
when I give it to her again.
你看  跟画上一模一样的笑容呢
Look, it's the same smile she has in the painting.
衣柜里有挂钩
Yeah-- there's hooks in the closet,
我现在就能帮你挂起来
I can hang it right now.
不用了  那些挂钩都不在了
Oh, no, no, Th-those hooks are gone.
怎么就不在了
What happened to them?
万圣节家里没糖果了
Uh, we ran out of candy on Halloween,
我就把各种东西拿来送了
I was just giving everything away.
你们俩怎么来...
Hey, guys, what are you...?
送这玩意儿来了  棒
Oh, that's here, cool.
艾米想要我留着
Amy wants me to have it.
如果我自己留着  那就太自私了
Well, it would be selfish of me to keep it.
但这画里有你
B-But it's a picture of you.
也有你
And you.
但是你请人画的
But you commissioned it.
画来送你
To give to you.
但你这么爱它
But you like it so much.
你也爱它啊
So do you.
我节节败退啊
I seem to be losing.
没错  的确是
Yes, you do.
莱纳德  我仔细想想之后想到
You know, Leonard, the more I think about it,
这公寓里有好多我们共同拥有的东西啊
there are a number of mutually owned items in this apartment
我们应该来过一遍所有权
that you and I should go through.
比如说
Uh, for example...
这把我们珍爱的《冰与火之歌》长爪宝剑
who gets our beloved sword, Longclaw?
要不你拿去吧
Why don't you keep it?
这挺合理  毕竟我们刚把画让给你们了
That seems fair; we did just give you the painting.
家里不用留任何能让我切腹自尽的物品
Yeah, I don't need anything around that I can stab myself with.
太好了  长爪剑是我的啦
Wonderful, Longclaw is mine.
那要不你留下我们的...
And how about you keep our...
牛油果盆栽
avocado plant?
很合理啊  一把价值几百美元的
Sounds right-- a limited edition collectible
限量版收藏品
worth hundreds of dollars
换从垃圾堆里捡来的破烂长出的所得物
and a thing that grew out of a thing we fished from the trash.
不过...  我跟艾米刚搬入新窝
Although, Amy and I did just move in together,
一盆植物是很好的新居礼物呢
and a plant is a lovely housewarming gift.
行  你把植物也拿走吧
Fine, take the plant.
我们有剑又有植物
Oh, we got a sword and a plant;
咱们的小窝渐渐成型啦
our apartment's really shaping up.
斯图尔特  你不用送我们怀孕礼物啦
Stuart, you didn't have to get us a baby gift.
就只是一些自制的兑换劵  上面有一些
Just homemade coupons for things you might need help with
宝宝生下来前你可能需要帮忙的事
before the baby gets here.
帮忙去超市买菜  开车载你去看医生
Going to the grocery store, driving you to the doctor.
如果不着急  我可以帮忙你挖个锦鲤池
If you're not in a hurry, I can dig you a koi pond.
还有脚底按摩吗
A foot massage?
这不是我在耍变态  你们俩谁用都行
And that's not me being creepy, that's for either of you.
你人真好  谢谢你  斯图尔特
This is very nice, Stuart, thank you.
为什么兑换劵是写在一张驱逐令的后面
How come this one's on the back of an eviction notice?
是啊  既然你刚好提到这事情...
Oh, yeah. Uh, now that you mention it...
我能住在这里吗
can I live here?
斯图尔特  我们很乐意帮忙你
Stuart, we'd love to help you out,
但现在真的不合适  我们马上要有孩子了
but this a bad time; we're about to have a baby.
但也正因为如此  所以是好时候啊
Or is that why this is a great time?
你们想想  孩子生下来以后
Think about it-- when that baby comes,
你们会非常需要人手帮忙
you're gonna need all the help you can get.
谢谢
Thank you,
但还是别了吧...
but I'm not really sure.
等等  或许这主意也不是那么糟
Hang on, maybe it's not the worst idea.
毕竟他当时照顾我妈的时候也做得很好啊
I mean, he did do a good job taking care of my mother.
打从由我负责撒爽身粉
That woman didn't get heat rash once
她再也没长过疹子
with me on powder patrol.
那要不先让你住几天
I guess you could stay for a few days
我们看看再说吧
and we'll see how it goes.
谢谢
Thank you.
只是暂时借住而已
And it's only temporary,
待我站稳脚跟  东山再起
just till I get back on my feet.
或是宝宝要去上大学了
or the baby goes off to college,
看哪件事先发生吧
whichever happens first.
你什么时候搬进来
When would you move in?
我的车在你们车道抛锚了
Well, uh, my car broke down in your driveway,
大概是现在搬进来吧
so I'm gonna say now.
但我已经准备帮忙了
But I am ready to be helpful.
其实
In fact...
我现在就去吸地板
I'm gonna go vacuum.
我今早才吸过一遍
Actually I just did that this morning.
好吧
Okay.
那我去扫灰
Then I'll dust.
我也做完了
I did that, too.
那我去检查烟雾侦测器里的电池
Then I'll check the batteries in the smoke detectors.
霍华德刚检查完
Howard just did that.
没事  让他做吧
Yeah, let him do it.
还记得我们从漫展买到这个吗
Remember when we got this at Comic-Con?
当然
Oh, yeah.
斯波克报时钟
The Mr. Spock cuckoo clock.
生生不息繁荣昌盛  生生不息繁荣昌盛
Live long and prosper. Live long and prosper.
生生不息繁荣昌盛
Live long and prosper.
世界上仅此一座
It's one of a kind.
所以如果坏了  世界上就没了吗
So if it breaks there'd be none of it?
莱纳德
Well, Leonard,
这个该归谁呢
you know, who should keep this?
一方面  我比你更爱斯波克先生
On the one hand, I love Mr. Spock more than you do.
另一方面  我比你更喜欢钟表
On the other hand, I care more about clocks than you do.
所以你觉得这个该归你吗
So you think you should keep it?
我就住在对面
I'll be right across the hall.
你没准还能听到它报时呢
You'll probably be able to hear it.
你拿走吧  谢尔顿
Keep the clock, Sheldon.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-是谢谢你  -谢他干嘛
- Thank you. - Thank you?
现在
Oh, now...
这三维象棋该归谁
what about our 3-D chess set?
我猜猜  你想要
Let me guess, you want it.
没有啦
Well, no,
我只是觉得你不会想有东西时刻提醒你
I just didn't think you'd want a physical reminder
这一款游戏你这辈子都赢不了
of a game you never managed to win.
出于好心  我该把所有游戏都拿走
As a kindness, I should probably take all the games.
好呀  谢尔顿  你拿走吧
You know what, Sheldon, take it.
其实你可以把所有东西都拿走
In fact, you can have everything.
我真的不在乎
I really don't care.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
这些东西代表着我们曾经共度的时光
These items represent our shared times together.
-现在都归你了  -莱纳德
- Well, now they're yours. - Leonard....
你也知道接下来会怎么样
Well, you know what's gonna happen.
他会编个理由来说明
He's just gonna come up with some reason
为什么一切都该归他
why everything should be his.
你既然这么会预测我的举动
For a man so good at predicting my moves,
三维象棋怎么就下得这么烂呢
how come you stink at 3-D chess?
谢尔顿  你这样有点自私吧
Sheldon, you're-you're being a little selfish.
你干嘛不让莱纳德挑几样东西留下来
Why don't you let Leonard keep a few things?
我不善于分享又不是我的错
It's not my fault I'm bad at sharing;
谁让我没上过幼儿园呢
I skipped kindergarten.
知道吗
You know what?
有一样东西我的确想留下来
There is one thing I would like.
好啊  想要什么随便拿
Yeah, take whatever you want.
我想要留下...
I would like to keep...
我们公寓的官方旗帜
the official flag of our apartment.
可你压根不喜欢旗帜啊
But you don't even like flags.
我独爱这一面
Yeah, I like this one.
但这是我设计的
But I designed it.
但是我订购回来的  因为你在旗帜圈里"太有名"
But you made me order it because you were "Too well-known"
所以人们知道是你  就肯定会提价
in the flag community and they'd jack up the price.
但你根本不懂这旗帜的象征意义
But you don't even understand its symbolism.
我懂啊
Oh, I do.
蓝色的部分代表着你现在痛苦不堪
The-the field of blue represents you being miserable,
吐舌头的狮子意味着
and the lion sticking its tongue out means
我喜见乐闻
I'm happy about it.
走吧  艾米
Come along, Amy.
别人想我滚时我能感觉到
I know when I'm not wanted.
我不认为你真知道  但好吧
I don't think you do, but all right.
斯图尔特  你做饭了吗
Stuart, you cooked?
你怎么知道不是我做的饭
How did you know it wasn't me?
家里虽然只有三个人
There's only three people in this house,
我猜肚子的宝宝和拉杰  都不会猜你
and you'd still be my fifth guess.
拉杰来了
That's Raj.
你们坐
You guys relax,
我去开门
I'll get it.
面包快趁热吃点
Have some bread while it's still warm.
感觉就像我们有个管家
It's like we have a butler.
如果我有变蝙蝠衣  那我就是公子哥蝙蝠侠啦
If I had a Batsuit I'd be Bruce Wayne.
你有蝙蝠衣啊
You have a Batsuit.
那是睡衣  没有斗篷
It's pajamas, there's no cape.
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
斯图尔特  你在这里干什么
Hey, Stuart. What are you doing here?
我又住在这里啦
Oh, I'm living here again.
霍华德和伯纳黛特知道这事吗
Do, uh, Howard and Bernadette know?
还是像负鼠那样  住在墙壁里在夹缝中生存
Or is it like a possum in the walls kind of thing?
不  我需要个地方住
No, I needed a place to stay
而且宝宝快出生了
and, with the baby coming,
我觉得他们需要多个人手来帮忙
I figured they could use some extra help.
行吧
Okay, cool.
进来吧  晚餐做好了
Anyway, come on in, dinner's ready.
可我买了中餐外卖
Oh, but I bought Chinese takeout.
好吧
Oh, okay.
如果伯纳黛特希望她的脚踝更水肿
Well, if Bernadette wants her ankles to swell up even more,
她可以吃你买的啊
she can have that.
你那无线网能用吗
Is the Wi-Fi working for you?
稍等
Uh, hang on.
不能用  我点击了
I don't think so, I'm clicking on
"让小腹变平坦的小怪招"
"One weird trick for a flat belly,"
可我还停留在
but I'm still seeing
"长得像自家宠物的名人们"的页面
"Celebrities who look like their pets."
我知道了
Oh, I knew it,
谢尔顿改了无线密码
Sheldon changed the password.
真的假的
Are you sure?
现在的无线网名称是
Well, the new network name is,
"哈哈  栽我手里了吧"  所以...
"Ha ha ha, now I've got you," so...
不是谢尔顿  就是蓝精灵的格格巫
It's either Sheldon or Gargamel from The Smurfs.
混蛋
What a jerk.
你擅长报复  我们该怎么治治他
You're good at revenge; how do we get him back?
我的必杀技通常是
Well, my go-to move is usually
睡那人的男朋友
sleep with the person's boyfriend,
但我有点觉得自己已经这样做了
but I kind of feel like I'm already doing that.
谢尔顿  我知道你干了什么
Sheldon, I know what you did,
快把密码改回来
now change the password back.
天下竟有这种奇事
Well, powder me in sugar and call me a donut,
莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德大驾光临
if it isn't Leonard Hofstadter.
谢尔顿  我警告你
Sheldon, I'm warning you,
你玩的小把戏的我也会玩
I can play this game, too.
如果你玩小把戏和玩三维象棋的水准一样
If it's like your 3-D chess game,
那你可是在三个维度上都不自量力
then you're out of your length, width and depth.
艾米  拿药膏来
Amy, get the Neosporin,
有人被损得体无完肤啦
somebody just got burned.
好吧  我尽力了
All right, I tried.
"好吧  我尽力了"
"All right, I tried."
你应该用这句当你自传的书名
That should be the title of your autobiography.
有人被损得皮焦肉烂啦
Ooh, a second-degree burn.
我把药膏拿来了
I've got the Neosporin.
是谁受伤了
Who got hurt?
还好你的可爱可以弥补智商
It's a good thing you're cute.
我之前读到  准父母最好报班学习
So, I was reading how it's a good idea for new parents
婴儿心肺复苏术
to take an infant CPR class.
是啊  我们一直打算去
Yeah, we've been meaning to do that.
我认识一个可以上门授课的心肺复苏指导员
Oh, I know a CPR instructor who'll come to the house.
-那就太好了  -那我给他打个电话
- That'd be great. - I'll give him a call.
我在沙滩上睡觉时遇见他
We met when I was sleeping on the beach
他当时以为我死了
and he thought I was dead.
再次谢谢你做晚饭
Thank you again for cooking.
现在站一整天对我来说越来越辛苦了
It's getting tough for me to be on my feet all day.
你尽管好好休息放松
You just kick back and relax;
一切都包在我身上
I've got it all under control.
本来就有人承包这一切事宜了
Although it was already under control.
不好意思  你嘟囔的啥我没听清
I'm sorry, you mumbled something?
我只是说他们本来也有人帮忙
It's just that they've had plenty of help.
俗语说得好
Well, you know what they say --
"举全村之力  养好一个娃"
it takes a village.
他们早有全村人  用不着你
Well, they already had a village.
我怎么没见全村人抽空把婴儿床装好呢
I noticed the village couldn't find time to put the crib together.
没准全村人都忙着为新生儿调查
Yeah, well, maybe the village was too busy checking out
本地蒙特梭利早教中心的口碑好不好
the local Montessori school for the new arrival.
你是说儿童沙坑里有空啤酒瓶的那家吗
You mean the one with the empty beer bottles in the sandbox?
我们不去  劳您费心了
We'll pass, thank you.
想想办法啊  蝙蝠侠
Do something, Batman.
你这是在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
内衣裤要分开来洗啊
Separating my delicates.
你竟堕落到如此地步
This is the level you're stooping to.
不
No.
这才是我要堕落到的地步
This is the level I am stooping to.
公寓旗移至股间4格  将军
I believe that is flag to crotch four, checkmate.
轻松舒爽  胯下惠风和畅
Easy-peasy, ooh, so breezy.
有何贵干
Hey, what's up?
我是来装婴儿床的
I'm here to put the crib together.
不好意思  我已经装好了
Ooh, sorry, I already did it.
我觉得你可能没意识到这点
Oh, I don't know if you realize this,
但那婴儿床是我买的
but I bought that crib.
我在"谁特么鸟你网"上看到了
Oh, yeah, I read about that on WhoGivesACrap.Com
你为什么要对我百般刁难
Why are you being like this?
因为我关爱霍华德和伯纳黛特
Because I love Howard and Bernadette
如果我想死赖着不走  我得帮得上忙
and if I want to keep mooching off them, I need to be helpful.
在你来之前  这个孕期早就被我
Hey, this pregnancy had an emotionally-needy
这个情感空虚的电灯泡承包了
third wheel way before you came along.
谁规定电灯泡只能有一个
Why can't there be four wheels?
我不在的时候  你就是这么争宠的吗
Is this what you do when I'm not here,
你个说话句句在理的狐媚子
make really good points?
好吧  进来帮我给宝宝搭个秋千吧
Look-Look, just come in and help me build a baby swing.
谢谢
Thank you.
你如果饿了可以吃你昨晚买的外卖
If you're hungry you can eat your takeout;
没人稀罕吃
nobody touched it.
我想去跑步
I think I'm gonna go for a run.
你想一起来吗
You want to come?
不去  上次公园里那个老太太一直大喊
No, last time that old lady in the park kept screaming,
"妹子小心  那变态马上要追上你了"
"Watch out, he's right behind you."
您好
Hello?
你们好啊
Hey, how you doing?
您有什么事吗
Uh, can I help you?
我没什么事  不过谢谢你好心询问
I don't think so, but you're sweet for asking.
你在我们公寓里做什么
What-What are you doing in our apartment?
你们邻居租了间房给我  瘦得像电线杆
Oh, I rented a room from your neighbor, the tall guy...
穿着像未成年小宅男那个
dressed like a little boy.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
好吧  我不知道他是怎么跟您说的
Okay, uh, I don't know what he told you,
但您不能住在这
but you can't stay here.
床单已经都换成新的了
So, there are fresh linens on the bed and...
看来你们已经见过西奥多了
Well, now, I see you've met Theodore.
西奥多  这两个是你的新室友
Theodore, these are your new roommates,
莱纳德和佩妮
Leonard and Penny.
他们为人忠厚
They're very honest,
但我建议你把现金都收好
but I would not leave cash lying around.
谢尔顿  你这是在做些什么
Sheldon, what do you think you're doing?
这个月的房租我已经付过了
My room is paid up until the end of the month,
所以我想怎么样就怎么样
so I can do with it whatever I please,
包括以一块钱一晚的价格租出去
which includes renting it out for a dollar a night.
房价一夜回到解放前
It's like the '40s again.
好了  我不打扰你们了
Anyway, I'll leave you be.
我还得去
I have to...
他希望早上能有报纸看
He's expecting a newspaper in the morning.
原来这年头还有人在印报纸呢
Apparently, they still make them.
谢尔顿  你这么做太过份了
All right, Sheldon, this is over the line.
没错
That's true,
但如果我不这么过份
but had I done something under the line,
你们厨房里就不会出现一个
there wouldn't be a man in your kitchen
身上什么身份证明都没有的陌生人了
who can't produce a single form of ID.
我有张卖血的收据
Oh, oh, I have a receipt from a blood bank.
我是O型阴性血
I'm O-negative.
现在你们对他的了解我和一样多了
And now you know as much about him as I do.
伯纳黛特
Oh, hey, Bernadette,
这个秋千送了两种转动玩具
the swing comes with two different mobiles.
这些长颈鹿挺可爱的  你觉得呢
The giraffes are pretty cute, what do you think?
挺好  就用长颈鹿吧
Great, go with the giraffes.
然而...
Although...
斑马身上对比鲜明的条纹
the high contrast of zebra stripes
可能能更好地刺激宝宝发育
might provide better stimulus for a developing baby.
说得有道理  还是选斑马吧
Yeah, you're probably right, go with the zebras.
太有眼光了  大佬
Good choice, boss.
棕色鼻子  意为马屁精
跪舔菊花的时候鼻子沾到...
至少我的鼻子不是因为拍马屁才变棕色的
At least my nose is naturally brown.
你能替我去趟超市吗
Hey, could you please go to the market for me?
让斯图尔特或拉杰去嘛
Get Stuart or Raj to do it.
华仔  他俩替你代劳了所有事
Howie, they've been doing everything for you.
我知道
Mm, I know.
让我越来越看不起这两个家伙了
It's really making me lose respect for both of them.
你就去一趟嘛
Please just go to the store.
好吧
Fine.
有人要载我去买东西不
Who wants to drive me to the store?
-我去  -我去
- Me! - I'll do it!
让拉杰去
Take Raj.
斯图尔特要帮我涂脚指甲油
Stuart is supposed to paint my toenails.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我们应该去住酒店吗
Should we go to a hotel?
把他单独留在家里吗
And just leave him here alone?
也对  那我自己住酒店
Okay, I'll go to a hotel.
如果明早你还没死  记得短信通知我
Text me in the morning if you're still alive.
西奥多
Uh, Theodore,
你打算在这里住多久
how long are you planning to stay exactly?
多亏了我在你家沙发里找到的硬币
Oh, thanks to the coins I found in your couch,
比我想象中又多了一天
a day longer than I thought.
实在是太不像话了
This is ridiculous.
我好喜欢这幅画
I like the painting.
另一个人是你妈吗
Is that your mom?
谢尔顿  给我出来
Sheldon, get out here!
你小声点好不好
Will you keep it down?
你当我这儿开得是
What kind of vengeful bed and breakfast
吵吵嚷嚷的黑旅店吗
do you think I'm running?
我们一起生活了13年
We lived together 13 years.
你怎么能对我如此狠心
How can you be so awful to me?
我狠心吗
I'm being awful?!
你才是在我心上用力开一枪的人
You're the one who went out of your way to hurt me.
那是因为你太自私了
Because you were being selfish.
和你分财产可是件难事呢
Dividing our belongings is difficult.
有什么难的  我什么都不想要
Why? I said I didn't care!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
虽然不关我的事  不过听起来
It's none of my business, but it sounds like a lot
你们的怒气都是由爱而生的
of this anger is coming from love.
我谢谢你全家  没人要你说话
Yeah, thanks, but nobody asked you.
不管怎样我还是要说下去
Well, I'm just gonna keep on talking.
看起来  谢尔顿的搬走
Seems like, with Sheldon moving out,
让你的生活进入了一个新的阶段
you're in a new phase of your lives
所以你们选择了简单的大吵大闹
and it's easier to fight than to face the feelings
来掩饰你们对彼此的真感情
that you have for one another.
我觉得他说得有道理
I think he might be right.
另外  这位高人是谁啊
Also, who is that?
我必须承认
I have to admit,
与你分开  和艾米同居
leaving you to move in with Amy
比我想象中要难得多
has been harder than I thought it would be.
对我也一样
Well, for me, too.
你走了  一切都不同了
It's not the same with you gone.
如果你想找个新室友...
If you're looking for a new guy to live with...
-没门  -不用了  谢谢
-No! - We're good. Thank you.
没人打算回答我吗  好吧
So, no one's gonna tell me? Okay.
莱纳德  我希望能停止
Leonard, I would like us to
这场财产争夺之战
stop fighting about our possessions.
举双手同意
Well, I'd like that, too.
我希望你能保留我们的公寓旗
In fact, I want you to keep the apartment flag,
我这么说并不仅仅是
and I'm not just saying that
因为你用生殖器磨蹭过它
because it touched your genitals.
你说真的吗
You promise?
我保证
I do.
为了表示我内心真的没有芥蒂
And to show you that there are no hard feelings,
我还愿意用我的生殖器磨蹭那旗子
I am willing to rub my genitals on it as well.
哎哟喂
Well...
说到用鸟磨蹭东西  这可是我的强项
if we're rubbing genitals on things, that's where I shine.
左边往下点
Little lower to the left.
再往下点
A little more.
好了吗
Is it good?
没用  还是丑得犯罪
No, still hideous.
我相信不久的将来
Well, I'm sure at some point,
我们就会完全忽略它的存在了
we won't even notice it's there.
你想得挺美
Yeah, you'd think that,
但不久它就会出现在你的噩梦里
but after a while it starts showing up in your dreams.
我觉得它让整个房间熠熠生辉
I think it brings the room together.
明天谁愿意粉刷婴儿室
Hey, tomorrow who wants to paint the nursery?
我做
I'll do it.
凭什么让你做啊
Why do you get to do it?
我可是个艺术家
I'm the artist.
你吃不饱饭
Just because you're starving
不等于你就是个艺术家
doesn't make you an artist.
我一脸菜色也不等于我吃不饱饭啊
Just because I look sickly doesn't mean I'm starving.
霍华德
Howard!
两位听到没  快去看看她要干嘛
Guys, you heard her, go see what she wants.
我好像快生了
I think I'm in labor.
哎呀  哎呀
Oh, oh, okay.
好的  那个那个  包在我身上
Okay, uh, uh, uh, I can do this.
我们早有准备
We have a plan.
谁来告诉我需要准备什么
Somebody please tell me the plan.
-我去拿待产包  -我去发动车
- I'll get the hospital bag. - I'll pull the van up.
2分钟后门外集合
Meet you outside in 2 minutes.
宝宝特工队  行动
Team Baby, go!
我真的好爱你
I love you.
我也好爱你
I love you, too.
你俩是要抱个没完  还是要生孩子
Are we hugging or having a baby?
快走
Let's go!